now that we have seen a two-bit
predictor and how it works let's do a
quiz on two bit predictors let's say you
have a two-bit predictor that has the
four states the 0 state is the strong
not taken then we have the weak not
taken weak taken and the strong taken
State let's say that we start in the
strong not taken State and remember that
if we have a taken decision we move
towards the strong taken State and stay
there as long as we have a taken
decision but for a not taken decision we
can't down towards the strong not taken
State and stay there the question for
you is is there a sequence of Branch
outcomes that results in never
predicting correctly so is there a
sequence such that when we start in this
state and here obviously we're
predicting not taken so the outcome
needs to be taken and then after we
update the predictor we have to
mispredict again and again if yes there
is a sequence then write the first five
outcomes of that sequence here if no
then put a check mark here